bizwatchnigeria.ng 2016-10-18

# Privacy Policy | BizWatchNigeria.Ng

## **Introduction**

**Thanks for visiting**[ **www.bizwatchnigeria.com**](http://www.bizwatchnigeria.com/) **. Bizwatchnigeria.com and** its advertisers are committed to protecting the privacy of internet users.

Consequently, our Privacy Statement is available to let users in on our collection and use of personal information so that they can make informed choices about how their information is collected and used. This Privacy Statement reflects the Bizwatchnigeria.com policies governing personal information collected at this website from the commencement of our routine operations onward.

Be it information collated from consumers conducting transactions or information collected on behalf of our business clients, it is our belief that information used responsibly benefits both the consumers and the economy. For example, we use consumer information to better serve our visitors and subscribers by offering goods and services, and channelling communication that we believe fit their needs, interests and aspirations.

When identifying an opportunity, Bizwatchnigeria.com may use consumer information it has collected in an effort to identify consumers who may be interested in that opportunity. Each day, we and our employees and agents strive to reinforce this commitment to our clients and consumers.

In keeping to this commitment, we ensure that we abide by the set of privacy policies outlined below, which guide us in the collection and use of information, and stipulate our employees’ responsibilities in protecting the privacy of our visitors and subscribers.

### **Collection of personally identifiable information for memberships**

Bizwatnigeria.com collects information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you will be required to enter your name, business/industry sector, e-mail address or phone number. Subscription with your email address to receive our regular newsletters is optional and you must be 18 years or older before you can register yourself. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### **Collection of non-personally identifiable information**

Bizwatchnigeria.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the IP-address you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). This information is used to improve the website by – for example – analyzing which pages are popular and which pages need to be improved. The non-personally identifiable information is not sold to any third-parties.

### **Our use of Your Information**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one or more of the following ways:

To personalize your experience by responding to your individual needs; to improve our website by modifying our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you; to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site features; to send periodic emails and/or our daily newsletters.

 If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### **Use of cookies by Bizwatchnigeria.com**

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow), which enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

At Bizwatchnigeria.com we use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. For instance, we use cookies to store information about the country and city from which you are surfing. This information is used to customise the website – content as well as advertisements – according to your geographical location.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

 In all cases, you can stop this usage of cookies by Bizwatchnigeria.com by disabling cookies in your browser.

In general, you can use Bizwatchnigeria.com without cookies although it might reduce the user-friendliness of the portal.

### **Usage of cookies by Advertisers**

Bizwatchnigeria.com runs advertisements from various renowned advertising networks such as Google. Their usage of cookies is governed by the individual privacy policy of the advertising network in question.

For instance, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to Bizwatchnigeria.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

A good resource to learn more about your consumer privacy in relation to these advertising networks is the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). On this website you can opt out from Behavioural Advertising for all the advertising networks which are members of the NAI.

### **Disclosure of Information**

Bizwatchnigeria.com does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe the release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our rights, property, or safety, or those of others. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. ****

### **Recipients of Information**

Bizwatchnigeria.com may disclose consumer information to companies affiliated with Bizwatchnigeria.com and to companies or other parties not affiliated with Bizwatchnigeria.com (subject to consumers’ opt-out rights). These recipients include financial institutions such as banks, credit card companies and brokerage houses, government agencies and other such recipients permitted by the Nigerian law.  

### **Confidentiality of Personal Consumer Information**

Bizwatchnigeria.com limits access to personal information to those employees of Bizwatchnigeria.com and its affiliates who need it to fulfil their business responsibilities and obligations. Employees must adhere to Bizwatchnigeria.com privacy policies. Employees who violate these policies will be subject to disciplinary action and may be dismissed. Vendors and other outside contractors engaged by Bizwatchnigeria.com are subject to our contractual requirements to ensure that sensitive personal information is safeguarded.

### **Opt Out Right**

Bizwatchnigeria may disclose consumer information to third parties as described earlier in this notice. Many of these disclosures are beneficial to consumers because they permit goods and services of interest to consumers to be offered to them at attractive rates. We strive to give consumers choices about how their data will be used. As a consumer, you have the right to opt-out of (i.e. direct us not to make) these disclosures when the consumer information is about you. Of course, there are some disclosures to third parties that are not subject to the opt-out, such as disclosures necessary to effect, administer or enforce a transaction requested by you, to companies that perform services for us or to prevent fraud. When you use this service, you will be asked whether you wish to opt out. If you wish to opt out, you may simply click the appropriate box and submit your choice.

### **Third Party Links**

We will regularly include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

###   **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of this portal.

### **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may send your enquiries to: info@bizwatchnigeria.com 

### **Your Consent  
**

By using this site, you consent to our privacy policy. If we decide to alter anything on our privacy policy, we will post those alterations on this page.

We may alter this statement as needed for certain products and services and to abide by local laws or regulations around the world. We also reserve the right to amend or modify this statement from time to time. You may change your choices at any time.
